An express bus fell off a bridge.
Twelve have lost their lives.
One male passenger is still missing.
Your husband was having an affair
with my wife.
They were sitting next to each other.
I'm sorry.
You're just the same height as him.
NAGANO PREFECTURAL POLICE
Hello.
That's right.
Yes.
What?
Yes, of course.
Thank you, bye.
They say the search has been called off.
That means…
Mitsuru
was apparently not on the bus.
What?
Please take a look at this.
The man who just got on.
Yes, that's my husband.
And here.
The same man is getting off.
What?
Right after this,
the bus departs without him returning.
That means,
my husband wasn't on the bus
at the time of the accident.
His luggage was still there,
and he seemed flustered,
so I think there must have been
some reason for getting off.
Before he got back on,
security cameras captured him
buying something at the rest area,
but he didn't seem to behave
out of the ordinary.
He got off on his own.
Why?
Maybe he was trying to save himself.
I mean, right after that,
the crash happened.
Are you saying Mitsuru killed them?
-How?
-No, that's not what I'm saying.
I just thought it looked that way.
Anyway…
now that we know
he got off the bus on his own,
we're calling off the search
at the accident site.
Right.
But you'll still be
looking for him, right?
Like asking around at the rest area?
There are no signs of a crime,
so we can't conduct an active search.
But he hasn't come home.
He might have collapsed somewhere.
Is it possible that he ran away?
Ran away?
It happens a lot. Those who elope…
I mean, people who try to escape
their current lives and disappear.
We'll be preparing a statement,
so please wait here.
Excuse us.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's not like he was trying to save
himself or anything. I'm really sorry.
Should we rent a car nearby?
Rent a car?
To get to the rest area.
I'm not so keen on taking the bus.
I mean,
your husband is probably still alive.
We have to look for him.
Azusa's death was an accident
caused by the driver's sudden illness.
It's frustrating, but I've accepted that.
But still,
why she got on that bus,
and why her travel partner was gone,
those are the things
I want to fully understand.
Right now,
I want to see your husband
more than you do.
Even if we do see him,
please don't punch him right away.
Maybe I will.
No, you won't!
I have to punch him first.
Oh, is that how you want it?
I most certainly want to see him
more than you do.
Well, that's fine then.
-Yes.
-Thank you, sir.
-Please drive safely.
-Got it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Can I make a quick phone call?
Sure.
Hello, Naoto.
I see.
That's great.
Or maybe not.
It's hard to know how to react, right?
But the chances that he's alive
have gone up by a lot.
I just thought I should let you know.
Thank you.
Let me know if you hear from Mitsuru.
If he's in a position to contact me,
he would call you first.
Not necessarily.
For Mitsuru
to put me above all else in everything,
that's so not like him.
If anything happens,
I'll contact you right away.
Thank you.
Sakiko, are you okay?
Eat well, will you?
Mrs. Seo!
I've set the GPS.
Should we head out now?
Yes, of course.
Sorry, Naoto, what did you say?
Are you going for a drive?
Oh, no.
I thought of going to the service area
where Mitsuru got off.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you. Bye.
Bye.
Take care of yourself, seriously…
-Sorry about that.
-It's okay.
Hey.
What happened to your smartphone?
You mean, my wife's?
Yes.
It's broken. It won't turn on.
Not getting it fixed?
Why, so we can pry into it for clues?
Does your husband still have his phone?
It seems he left it on the bus.
It's completely wrecked,
so don't count on it.
You won't have it fixed?
If the phone worked,
I would be scared to find something.
And if I found nothing,
I would feel guilty.
I get that.
I was actually relieved
it wouldn't turn on.
I know, right?
But I guess the stuff they left behind
feels more credible.
What, you don't trust
other people's testimonies?
I just can't quite wrap my head around
what Naoto said to me.
I can't imagine Mitsuru
complaining to him about me.
Wow.
You're very sure about that.
I'm sure he had some kind of grievance.
It's just that I can't imagine him
venting to Naoto.
Why?
Mitsuru is very considerate
of other people's perspectives.
As an employer,
he considers inconveniencing people,
even over trivial stuff,
as power harassment.
That's why,
no matter how dissatisfied
he might be with me,
I didn't think he would vent at Naoto.
That's amazing.
Indeed, he is.
He's the kind of person
who always thinks about others.
For that I respect him.
That's not what I meant.
As much as you praise your husband,
can you really trust him that much?
I see.
You know the current state of affairs.
He missed the bus, right?
Yet, he didn't come home,
so even before we can get into whether--
He ran away from his wife?
The reason I'm blabbering on like this
is because if I stop thinking,
I might go crazy.
Even so, I believe in Mitsuru.
Believe in what, exactly?
That he's not having an affair,
or that he didn't run away?
Both.
I mean, Mitsuru…
He proposed to me, didn't he?
He asked me to marry him.
For crying out loud.
I've been here before.
With the man who proposed to you?
How did you know?
I could tell by your face.
By my face?
The security camera caught him
shopping somewhere, didn't it?
Um…
It was a curry bread specialty shop,
and he bought two, they said.
Should we check it out?
Do you have a photo?
Right.
How about this one?
It's from about two months ago.
-Something like this?
-The first one is better.
Okay.
Oh, look.
Is this the place?
Yeah…
They only have one item on the menu.
Want to grab one? I sure do.
Mrs. Seo.
I'll have one.
Well…
it was to be expected.
With hundreds of customers each day,
there's no way they'd remember every face.
So, now what?
Should we ask at the other shops?
Are you even listening?
This…
I ate it with Mitsuru, too.
Really?
It's pumpkin.
I can see that.
Did Azusa like pumpkin?
Yes, she did.
I see.
Yes.
Once we were both having this,
and we got all excited, saying,
"Wow, there's pumpkin!"
You don't like pumpkin?
I like it, actually.
It's Mitsuru who doesn't.
I see.
Then why did he buy it again?
I assume he bought it for Azusa.
I kept saying how delicious it was
until I gobbled up Mitsuru's portion.
He probably knew that
pumpkin lovers will find it delicious.
But he bought two, right?
Maybe he just forgot
that these have pumpkin in it?
Right.
He probably got one for himself
and one for Azusa.
And he had forgotten
about eating these with me.
That was delicious.
I'll buy some to take home.
Sorry, now you even have to go through
the trouble of returning the car.
No, I was planning to drive this
straight to my parents'.
I see.
I'm glad to hear that.
Does Sho like pumpkin?
Yes, he likes it.
Then, give him this as a souvenir.
No, that's yours.
I would be happy
if someone who likes pumpkin could eat it.
-Well then, thank you.
-Yes.
Well…
If I find something on the phone,
I'll let you know.
What?
I'm going to get it fixed.
Wow.
I won't make you have hers fixed.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
Take care.
"Take care"…
YAMURAMACHI STATION
Sorry.
I got in a car, sitting next to the driver
who's a man.
You thought if you sat in the back,
it would seem like
you were being too polite
and make him feel like
he had to be considerate.
Yes.
I was torn about it when I got in.
You're so kind,
always thinking about others.
Do you actually like pumpkin?
No. I'm not a fan.
I thought so.
You know,
that time when there was about
one serving of curry left in the pot,
so I…
microwaved some bite-sized
frozen pumpkin cubes,
added them to the curry, and ate it.
I didn't know that. Was it good?
Yes.
It tasted good, but…
I felt I had to finish it
before you got home,
so I ate it in a hurry.
Why? You didn't do anything wrong.
Yes, but…
I made it on the sly
and ate it on the sly.
It's something I like,
but you don't.
It was a curry
tailored to both of our tastes,
that we made together
and ate together.
So when I did that with the leftovers…
I knew it wasn't wrong,
but I felt like I had to hide it.
I see.
When you were
meeting Azusa every month,
did you feel the same?
-Sho.
-Daddy!
Fist bump, fist bump, high-five, hug!
Have you been a good boy?
-Yes.
-Good.
Look.
What is it?
What?
This isn't the one I gave you
for your birthday.
She bought this for me
because I'm a good boy.
I'm sorry.
You're already busy taking care of Dad.
It's fine.
Daddy, when are you coming back again?
We'll be going back to our home in Tokyo.
Hey, Sho.
Daddy is driving today.
Wanna ride home with me?
Not in a car
you don't know who's been in it.
Sho, let's go take a bath.
-Get your pajamas ready.
-Okay.
Don't try to win his affection
by buying him things.
Azusa didn't like that, either.
I just felt bad for Sho
because Azusa had been unnaturally strict.
It's just normal discipline.
Every family is like that.
She wouldn't know what normal is.
She wasn't raised in a normal household.
-That's exactly my point.
-What?
Have you ever talked to Azusa herself
about the environment she grew up in?
I don't remember.
Are you just being insensitive--
What's that? A souvenir?
What?
I got curry bread to give to Sho.
From the woman you went out with?
What?
You've got to be careful with that car.
A woman's scent may linger.
That's not what's going on.
For a five-year-old
to receive such greasy food…
She doesn't have kids, does she?
Isn't that great?
You could think about remarrying.
Never mind.
Ta-da!
Hey, Sho.
When shall we go back to Tokyo?
Maybe tomorrow?
Is Mommy coming back tomorrow?
I don't think she'll be back tomorrow.
Oh…
Then, I want to stay here.
What?
SAKIKO SEO
THANK YOU FOR ACCOMPANYING ME TODAY.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT. NO NEED TO REPLY.
-Hey.
-Your kid still at your parents'?
-Yes.
Instead of leaving him there
for the weekend,
you should take him out somewhere,
before his grandma takes over.
I guess you're right.
He's five, right?
It's too hot outside,
so I would recommend indoor places.
What kind of indoor places can he play in?
Like KidZania,
the Anpanman Children's Museum,
or Sanrio Puroland.
Hold on, let me jot those down.
All right.
Well, KidZania, Anpanman…
Or an aquarium, to play it safe.
Well…
KidZania, Anpanman, what was it again?
Puroland.
The one with Hello Kitty.
So that's indoors?
Yes, but I would still
recommend the aquarium.
It's relaxing for adults,
and it's near the station.
I see…
I've never been to KidZania.
It sounds fun.
Excuse me,
and thank you for your patience.
Here you go.
Thank you so much.
What's the passcode for this?
Well…
I'm sorry,
but we don't unlock phones here.
I see.
I see. Thanks.
First, his birthday…
ENTER PASSCODE
I'm scared.
So, you're stumped?
I tried his birthday and our wedding
anniversary, but they didn't work.
What about you?
What?
What's your phone's passcode?
Um…
Wait…
I won't try it, okay?
I'm just gathering info on what
men base their four-digit passcodes on.
It's Sho's weight at birth: 3,075 grams.
Oops, I said it.
So, it's not your birthday?
If I used the birth date,
others would likely find out easily.
But birth weight? Not so much.
I see, but your parents might know.
I think Azusa
could have figured it out easily.
So you're saying you have nothing to hide.
It's also a way of showing that.
Showing what?
A password my wife
could figure out easily, you know.
It doesn't seem like
I'm hiding anything, right?
Besides, it's tied to our son.
I see…
So that means…
Mitsuru is indeed…
You've gotten pretty timid, haven't you?
You used to trust him so much,
just because he proposed to you.
Without rhyme or reason,
you ingenuously placed your faith in him.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm free to believe what I want.
But the way you see it,
I suppose it's all wishful thinking.
I don't know all the details yet,
but there's no denying
that Mitsuru was with your wife.
And yet, only he survived.
I'm so sorry.
There's no use apologizing for that.
Let's find him
and make him apologize in person.
So, what should we do next?
Maybe put up a flyer?
You see those for lost pets all the time--
I'm so sorry.
I do feel like
giving Mitsuru a big "Screw you!"
but you didn't do anything wrong,
so no need to apologize.
He's my family.
I'm his wife.
So, I'm responsible, too.
I knew someone from college,
the same year as mine,
who struggled with job hunting
because his brother had a criminal record.
I always thought it was weird,
because he was a fine guy.
He had cut ties with his junkie brother,
and of course, never did drugs himself.
Maybe that wasn't the best example.
Anyway, I won't take
my anger toward Mitsuru out on you.
If you find him,
you go first.
You mean, punch him? Me first?
Yes.
Suddenly, I'm feeling more motivated.
I'll do whatever it takes to find him.
Yes.
What about you?
What's your passcode?
I already gave mine. Just spill it.
It's 0317.
Mitsuru's birthday.
You really love him.
"How to find a missing person."
The police…
A private investigator…
Or through social media--
Oh, no!
Geez.
Oh, dear.
What will you do, now that I'm gone?
Can you get that stain out?
No, I can't.
Why don't you just
cut out the stained part?
Really?
So it'll show a little skin
and make it sexy?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You know,
the T-shirt you gave me?
Yes.
It's fantastic.
You're the pickiest man in Japan
when it comes to T-shirts.
And this one is perfect.
The size…
the thickness of the fabric,
how snug the neckline is…
Isn't it?
Where did you buy it?
Online.
You can only get it
from the brand's official online store.
It takes some time to arrive
after ordering.
That type of shop.
Maybe I should stock up on some of this.
Coming.
-Delivery.
-Sure.
Thank you, sir.
It's for you, Azusa.
What did you buy?
I'll just open this, okay?
Sorry, that's your favorite…
48TH MUSASHINO
SUMMER FIREWORKS FESTIVAL
A fireworks festival?
COUPLE'S SEAT
-Good morning.
-Morning.
Chizuru.
Yes?
Perhaps it's time
you entrusted me with a major project.
I'm kind of idle.
Everyone else seems so busy,
and I feel kind of guilty.
Well…
If that's what you want, Sakiko.
Thank you.
It's okay. I know he will come back.
Okay.
Hey, Rino.
Yes?
I have tickets for the fireworks festival.
You can go with your partner.
They're for so-called "couple's seats."
Really?
I would love to go.
Great. Here you go.
SUMMER FIREWORKS FESTIVAL
Oh, dear. I'm so sorry.
I already have plans for that day,
so I can't go.
I see. Got it.
Why would you have tickets
to a fireworks festival?
I found them inside Mitsuru's jacket.
What?
Tickets for next month's festival.
Two of them. Couple's seats.
Wow.
-Hey.
-What?
If there's something
you don't want your wife to see,
where would you hide it?
I don't have anything like that.
I knew it.
Why did you ask?
Well…
-In that case…
-Yes?
What if you want to go
somewhere your wife doesn't like,
but you would feel awkward going alone?
Well…
I would go with you.
I thought so too!
That is so not helpful.
Don't you think so-called normal couples
end up on bad terms with each other
because they make each other
hide things from one another?
Oh. Good point.
Sakiko.
That's all I need.
Just find a good spot to leave off.
So, I'll do it until there.
Thank you.
Since you can't go and hire a part-timer
all by yourself.
Yeah, that's true.
Maybe I should just hire you.
Go ahead and hire me.
Go ahead, just take over the shop.
Sorry about my husband.
It's tough being married, isn't it?
You didn't do anything wrong, Sakiko.
It can't be helped.
We're family, after all.
Family, or rather, a married couple?
Yes.
Wait.
A married couple is a family, right?
But you were strangers to begin with.
And now, we're a married couple.
Not strangers anymore.
I left the sign out front.
Hold on.
Got it.
Hello, this is Café Hikoki.
Hello?
What?
They hung up
I see.
That happens sometimes. Prank calls.
My, that's awful.
Naoto.
Yes?
Can I take Mitsuru's apron home?
I want to wash it.
Where's the kid?
My mother is caring for him at her place.
I see.
She's supportive.
What a wonderful family.
This one, isn't it cute?
It was Azusa
who gave it to me.
She said that old people
could actually die from the heat.
Azusa once said,
it was so weird
that she thought it was broken,
so she gave it away.
Guess who got it.
Really…
Right.
These
are your wife's belongings
that she left at the store.
Here you go.
Right. Sorry you had to do this.
No, it's no big deal.
I could've taken them that day.
No, I hadn't sorted through them yet.
Besides that,
I still needed some time
to sort out my own feelings.
ENTRY PASS
The aquarium.
Yes.
Azusa was a fan of aquariums, wasn't she?
Even during her break,
she would constantly
look up all sorts of places.
-What, is something off?
-What?
No.
Is it weird for a woman
to want to go to the aquarium?
No…
Right, there were two tickets.
Perhaps she was planning to go with you.
There aren't any kids' tickets.
Maybe you just wanted
to spend time alone together.
Oh, tea.
Or do you prefer coffee?
-Yes.
-Got it.
About this mini fan.
Yes?
Why didn't you ask her,
"Who did you give it to?" or something?
Weren't you curious?
No, my wife would bring up things
she wanted to talk about on her own.
You have no idea
what she was like at home.
There was a certain distance
between us as a couple.
Yeah, I can see that.
My apologies, it looks like
this old man's getting a little too nosy.
Her catchphrase at home was,
"Hey, Itsuki, listen."
When I got home first, for instance,
she'd start talking about almost anything
before I even closed the front door.
I see.
She would often tell me after the fact.
Sometimes I would ask,
"You went there?" or "You bought that?"
That kind of spontaneous,
free-spirited vibe.
That was Azusa at home.
I see.
I'm pretty sure
she would have told me about it that day.
"Hey, Itsuki, listen."
"Today, I joined one of our neighbors,
that is Mr. Seo, on a bus trip to Nagano."
And?
"You see,
I met Mr. Seo about half a year ago
at the coin laundry, and…"
We often chat
while waiting for the laundry to finish.
I told you about it, right, Itsuki?
That delicious soba restaurant
in Nagano I saw on Brunch.
When I mentioned it to Mr. Seo,
he was like,
"I've been wanting to go there too."
and then I said, "Oh, let's go together."
Sorry.
Sometimes I just want to
get away from Tokyo,
get out in nature and relax, for a change.
I meant to inform you before I left,
but Miki had just offered
to hang out with Sho.
And for me to go out with another man
at such a time…
I feared if I told your mom about that,
she might get the wrong idea.
Or so I overthought.
So I had to tell you after the fact.
But…
Yes, he's a man, but there's really
nothing going on between us.
We just chat once a month
at the coin laundry.
Today was the first time we met
somewhere else.
Oh…
We did sit next to each other on the bus.
I'm really sorry about that.
"I thought you would believe me, Itsuki,
so I'm going to tell you the truth.
You'll believe me, right?"
That's what she would say.
Wow.
-That was wonderful. Thank you.
-Yes.
It was entertaining.
Well…
You don't mind barley tea?
Well then, in that case,
I'm taking back what I said earlier.
I just thought it wasn't right
to twist the deceased's past
for the sake of those left behind.
Let me just say this.
Yes?
We used to chat a lot
while we were working.
Well…
Back then,
your wife would love to say…
"Hey, boss."
"Listen, I can't tell my husband this."
That's all.
I have to go now. Bye.
Maybe I'm using Azusa's death
as an excuse to romanticize
both myself and her too much.
SHINAGAWA AQUARIUM
ENTRY PASS
I just simply hate aquariums.
Azusa knew that
really well.
I just simply hate fireworks festivals.
Mitsuru knows that
really well.
Wow.
Maki is getting married.
Our wedding date…
June 28th…
I felt bad about
breaking into Mitsuru's phone,
worried that he might get mad
when he comes home.
But it's okay.
He probably…
This is Café Hikoki.
…won't come home.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
That happens sometimes. Prank calls.
My, that's awful.
Mitsuru…
isn't coming back.
Apparently, she went to the service area.
With that other guy.
It's going to be all right.
It seems she's even able to go to work.
It may have been a coincidence,
but aren't you glad you got to
hear her voice a little?
It made me really nervous, though.
If you're that worried,
why don't you just come home,
Mr. Seo?
Subtitle translation by: Frederick